[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Steven Valenzuela, Jiles Perry Richardson, and Charles Hardin Holley are all better known by different professional names. What else do they have in common?", "correct_answer": "They died together in a plane crash.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were all, at different times, married to the same woman.", "They have all won Academy Awards.", "They are all best-selling novelists."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This freshwater-lake island, with a surface area of 2,766 km\u00b2, is the biggest on Earth.", "correct_answer": "Manitoulin Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Islandlake", "Ainslie", "Isle of Wight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to her autobiography, who did John Huston tell Hepburn to model her portrayal of Rose after, in the movie, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "Eleanor Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Aimee Semple MacPherson", "Amelia Earhardt", "Mary Pickford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is given credit  for being the first person to reach the North Pole?", "correct_answer": "Peary", "incorrect_answers": ["Bering", "Amundsen", "Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The hands and feet have the most bones in the human body.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these religious organisations are notorious for their suicides motivated by religious and spiritual beliefs. Mark the odd one.", "correct_answer": "THC Ministry", "incorrect_answers": ["Order of the Solar Temple", "Peoples Temple", "Heavens Gate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Braveheart, King Edward I was also referred to as Edward the Long Shanks?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mia, the protagonist of The Princess Diaries, celabrated her which birthday in the movie?", "correct_answer": "16th", "incorrect_answers": ["17th", "15th", "21st"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US President to die while in office?", "correct_answer": "William Henry Harrison", "incorrect_answers": ["John Tyler", "Martin Van Buren", "Andrew Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unusual anatomical feature does the male ostrich possess?", "correct_answer": "It has a copulatory organ.", "incorrect_answers": ["It has four testicles.", "It has a very small horn on its head.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animal can clean its own ears with its 21-inch tongue.", "correct_answer": "Giraffe", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizard", "Elephant", "Lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is an existing country, recognized by United Nations?", "correct_answer": "East Timor", "incorrect_answers": ["East Cyprus", "West African Republic", "West Virginia"]}]